Parapsychology Laboratory Records, 1893-1984
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Financial Papers Series, 1945-1962, 10 containers (5 lin. ft.)
  - 1947-1953
    - Office expenditures (Box 668)
    - Office expenditures, (2 folders) (Box 669)
    - Petty cash (Box 669)
    - Purchase orders (Box 669)
    - Summaries of expenditures (Box 669)
  - 1950ESP card quotations (Box 669)
  - 1950-1954, Rockefeller Foundation grant (Box 669)
  - 1953-1957
    - Budget data (Box 669)
    - Capital expenditures (Box 669)
    - Graduate Research Council grants, (2 folders) (Box 669)
    - McDougall Research Fund, (4 folders) (Box 670)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 670)
    - Office expenditures, (2 folders) (Box 670)
    - ONR contract, (2 folders) (Box 670)
    - ONR contract, (4 folders) (Box 671)
    - NSF application (Box 671)
    - Personnel (Box 671)
    - Petty cash (Box 671)
    - Repair and removal (Box 671)
    - Telephone and telegrams (Box 671)
  - 1957-1962
    - Accounts shown JBR (Box 671)
    - Budget data (Box 671)
    - Check stubs (Box 672)
    - Graduate Research Council grants, (2 folders) (Box 672)
    - McDougall Research Fund, (2 folders) (Box 672)
    - McDougall Research Fund, (3 folders) (Box 673)
    - Office expenditures, (5 folders) (Box 673)
    - ONR contract, (3 folders) (Box 674)
    - Personnel, (4 folders) (Box 674)
    - Petty cash (Box 674)
  - 1958-1961,Personal finances, (2 folders) (Box 674)
  - 1962, FRNM (Box 674)
- Clippings Series, C. 1935-1980, 7 containers (2.5 lin. ft.)
  Copies of clippings relating almost entirely to J. B. Rhine and the work of the Parapsychology Laboratory, or to its research interests. Many of Rhine's journal publications are included. There are also several Items on political topics, relating to Rhine's public affairs concerns. Arranged alphabetically by source of publication, then chronologically.
  - A, 1900-1970, (2 folders) (Box 675)
  - American Weekly, 1934-1943 (Box 675)
  - Atlanta Journal, 1935-1943 (Box 675)
  - B, 1930-1970, (2 folders) (Box 675)
  - C, 1930-1970, (2 folders) (Box 675)
  - D, 1930 to 1970, (2 folders) (Box 676)
  - Duke Chronicle, 1962-1968 (Box 676)
  - Durham Morning Herald and Sun, 1920-1980, (3 folders) (Box 676)
  - E, 1930-1970, (2 folders) (Box 676)
  - English, 1935-1938 (Box 676)
  - F, 1930 to 1970, (2 folders) (Box 677)
  - Foreign miscellaneous (Box 677)
  - French, 1950-1960 (Box 677)
  - G, 1930 to 1970 (Box 677)
  - German (Box 677)
  - H, 1930 to 1970, (2 folders) (Box 677)
  - I, 1930-1970 (Box 677)
  - J, 1930-1970 (Box 677)
  - K, 1930-1970 (Box 677)
  - L, 1930-1970, (2 folders) (Box 677)
  - Liberty Magazine (Box 678)
  - Liberty Digest, 1936-1937 (Box 678)
  - Life Magazine (Box 678)
  - Look Magazine (Box 678)
  - M, 1920-1970, (2 folders) (Box 678)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 678)
  - N, 1920-1980, (3 folders) (Box 678)
  - New York Herald Tribune, 1930-1960 (Box 678)
  - New York Times, 1938-1977, (3 folders) (Box 679)
  - New Yorker Magazine (Box 679)
  - O, 1930-1970, (3 folders) (Box 679)
  - P, 1930-1970, (3 folders) (Box 679)
  - Norman Vincent Peale, 1967 (Box 679)
  - Q, 1970 (Box 679)
  - R, 1930-1977, (3 folders) (Box 679)
  - Reader's Digest, 1955-1958 (Box 679)
  - S, 1930-1970, (3 folders) (Box 680)
  - Scandinavian, 1949-1961 (Box 680)
  - Science (Box 680)
  - Soviet Clippings, 1977 (Box 680)
  - Spanish (Box 680)
  - T, 1930-1970, (3 folders) (Box 681)
  - Thornton, Spencer V. (Box 681)
  - Time (Box 681)
  - U, 1937-1976 (Box 681)
  - Unknown (Box 681)
  - V, 1948-1972 (Box 681)
  - W, 1930-1970, (2 folders) (Box 681)
  - X-Z (Box 681)
- Journal of Parapsychology Records Series, 1942-1959, 18 containers (9 lin. ft.)
  Files of managing editor Dorothy Pope.
  - Correspondence, 1942-1958
    Largely routine correspondence on subscriptions and exchanges but including some on submissions, particularly in later years. Arranged chronologically by year, then alphabetically by correspondent.
    - 1942,A - Z, (3 folders) (Box 682)
    - 1943,A - Z, (4 folders) (Box 682)
    - 1944,A - Z, (4 folders) (Box 683)
    - 1945
      - A - O, (2 folders) (Box 683)
      - P - Z (Box 684)
    - 1946
      - A - Sm, (5 folders) (Box 684)
      - So - Z (Box 685)
    - 1947,A - Z, (4 folders) (Box 685)
    - 1948
      - A - C (Box 685)
      - D - Z, (5 folders) (Box 686)
    - 1949,A - D (Box 686)
    - 1950,H - Z, (3 folders) (Box 688)
    - 1951
      - A - L, (3 folders) (Box 688)
      - M - Z, (2 folders) (Box 689)
    - 1952
      - A - L, (3 folders) (Box 689)
      - M - Z, (3 folders) (Box 690)
      - Parapsychology Forum (Box 690)
    - 1953
      - A - G, (2 folders) (Box 690)
      - H - Z, (4 folders) (Box 691)
    - 1954
      - A - C (Box 691)
      - D - Z, (4 folders) (Box 692)
    - 1955
      - A - C (Box 692)
      - D - Z, (5 folders) (Box 693)
    - 1956 (Box 694)
      - A - R, (4 folders) (Box 694)
      - S - Z (Box 695)
      - Parapsychology Foundation (Box 695)
    - 1957
      - A - L, (3 folders) (Box 695)
      - M - Z, (4 folders) (Box 696)
    - 1958
      - A - C, (2 folders) (Box 696)
      - D - T, (5 folders) (Box 697)
      - U-Z (Box 698)
    - 1959
      - A - K, (4 folders) (Box 698)
      - L - Z, (5 folders) (Box 699)
      - Library list (Box 699)
  - Office Files, 1937-1963
    General files, including correspondence of Pope with members of the Journal Editorial Board (1942-47) and several ledger books (1942-58) containing records of Journal finances. There are also two files of personal correspondence with William Russell (1945-47) and a notebook recording events at the weekly Laboratory Research Meeting (1962-63).
    - 1937-1944,Early Journal documents (Box 700)
    - 1942-1947,Co-editors' correspondence (Box 700)
    - 1942-1958,Ledger books (10 volumes) (Box 700)
    - 1942-1959,Post office (Box 700)
    - 1943-1947,Correspondence with William Russell, (2 folders) (Box 701)
    - 1946-1947,Addressograph, (4 folders) (Box 701)
    - 1950, Society for Parapsychology (Box 701)
    - 1953-1959, Cambridge University Press (Box 701)
    - 1962-1963,Research Meeting notes (Box 701)
    - 1957 (Box 702)
      - Clippings (Box 702)
      - Constitution and By-Laws (Box 702)
      - Correspondence re Constitution (Box 702)
      - Membership lists (Box 702)
      - Minutes of first council meeting (Box 702)
    - 1958
      - Council correspondence, (2 folders) (Box 702)
      - First annual convention, (2 folders) (Box 702)
      - General correspondence (Box 702)
      - Membership list (Box 702)
      - PA interests inventory, (2 folders) (Box 703)
      - Things a PA secretary needs to know (Box 703)
    - 1959
      - Council correspondence (Box 703)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 703)
    - 1960
      - Convention (Box 703)
      - Council correspondence (Box 703)
    - 1961
      - Convention (Box 703)
      - Convention papers, (2 folders) (Box 703)
      - Council correspondence (Box 703)
      - Elections, (3 folders) (Box 704)
      - Membership committee (Box 704)
      - Membership lists (Box 704)
      - Program committee (Box 704)
    - 1962
      - Convention papers (Box 704)
      - Council correspondence, (2 folders) (Box 704)
      - Financial papers (Box 704)
      - Membership committee (Box 704)
      - Membership dues, (2 folders) (Box 704)
      - Elections (Box 704)
    - 1963,Miscellaneous (Box 704)
- Oversize Material
  - Correspondence Series
    - Johnson, Charles E. (Box OV1, Opaperfolder 1)
    - Adams, July 4, 1935 (Box 705)
    - Brown, Th. J. F., Oct. 7, 1936, (3 items) (Box 705)
    - James, Henry Jr., 1942 (Box 705)
    - Moynahan, C.E., July 30, 1945 (Box 705)
    - Fogel, Maurice, March 27, 1947 (Box 705)
    - Fisher, Joel E., 1964 (Box 705)
  - Research Files Series
    - Alphanumeric Files
      - E:76: Rhine, J. B., (3 items) (Box OV1, Opaperfolder 1)
      - B6: Woodruff, J.L., (2 items) (Box 705)
      - B30: Price, Margaret M., (2 items) (Box 705)
      - C22: Rhine-Stuart (Box 705)
      - E49: Gibson, E.P., (4 items) (Box 705)
      - E72: Rhine-Ownby (Box 705)
      - C37: Price, M.M., (2 items) (Opaperfolder 3)
      - C38: Rhine, J.B., (4 items) (Opaperfolder 3)
      - D1: Rhine, J.B., (2 items) (Opaperfolder 3)
      - E76: Rhine, J.B. (many items) (Opaperfolder 3)
    - Subject Files
      - Displacement/ Pratt, J. G., Soal Stewart analyses, 1951-52 (Box OV1, Opaperfolder 1)
      - PK:Reeves/High vs. low dice, 1934 (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Displacement: Soal Stewart analyses, 1951-52, (2 items) (Box 705, Opaperfolder 2)
      - Displacement: C.J. Analyses, 1950(several items) (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Sex Predictions, Gale Data 1960 (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Marchesi, K., 1 year precognition, 1948-49 (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Marchesi, K., Transoceanic ESP Experiment, 1939-1940, (3 items) (Opaperfolder 3)
      - PK/Frick 60 dice series, 1937(several items) (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Woodruff, Van Wie, Big and little dice, 1936, (2 items) (Opaperfolder 3)
    - Experimenter Files
      - Bevan, W. Heidelberg College study, 1948 (Box OV1, Opaperfolder 1)
      - Ellis, L.: Group vs. alone DT, 1948-49 (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Ellis, L.: Precognition runs, 1950 (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Gibson, E.P.: Barometer study, 1938-40(many items)
        - Gibson, E.P.: 1939 Watts Hospital (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Humphrey, B.: Drug trials, 1936-37 (Box OV1, Opaperfolder 2)
      - Humphrey, B.: Rhine-Humphrey, Terminal salience, 1941 (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Humphrey, B.: Interests and ESP, 1949, (2 items) (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Nielsen, W.: Precognition vs. clairvoyance, 1955 (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Nielsen, W.: Otani ESP Summary, 1963 (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Nielsen, W.: ESP and emotional variables, 1964(many items) (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Osis, K.: First cat experiment, 1952, (3 items) (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Pratt, J.G.: NY ESP trials, 1937(several items) (Box OV1, Opaperfolder 3)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Pratt-Woodruff PK experiment, 1940(many items) (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Humphrey-Pratt comparison of test procedures, 1941, (3 items) (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Gibson exploratory PK, 1946-48, (2 items) (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Reeves PK position effects, 1947, (2 items) (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Hand-picture token object tests, 1948-49(4 picture envelopes) (Box OV1, Opaperfolder 4)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Jessup ESP test, 1950 (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Homing writings, 1953-58, (5 items) (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Forwald Duke PK, 1957 (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Louwerens school experiment, 1959-61, (2 items) (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Ryal Papers, 1959-63 (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Chauvin papers, 1961-62, (2 items) (Box OV1, Opaperfolder 5)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Miscellaneous data, undated (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Rhine, J.B.: Drug studies, 1935-39 (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Stuart, C.E.: Miscellaneous, undated (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Urban-Kock: Electro-shock experiment, 1947-50, (4 items) (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Vasse, C.: Classroom GESP, 1955-58, (6 items) (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Bevan, Jack: Davidson College Series, 1948 (Box 705)
      - Bindrim, E.: Miscellaneous, 1946 (Box 705)
      - George, R.W.: Ward Sisler music experiment, 1946 (Box 705)
      - Gibson, E.P.: Precognition correspondence experiment, 1938, (13 items) (Box 705)
      - Gibson, E.P.: Gibson miscellany, 1938-39 (Box 705)
      - Gibson, E.P.: Barometer study, 1938-1940, (2 items) (Box 705)
      - Gibson, E.P.: Doubles around the dice, 1942-43, (4 items) (Box 705)
      - Gibson, E.P.: Dice studies, 1944 (Box 705)
      - Hornaday, J., PK-attitude, undated (Box 705)
      - Humphrey, B.: Various Drug trials, 1938-39, (3 items) (Box 705)
      - Humphrey, B.: Hutchison PDT, 1940, (10 items) (Box 705)
      - Humphrey, B., Rhine-Humphrey, salience ratios, 1941, (5 items) (Box 705)
      - Humphrey, B.: Salience ratios in Gibson correspondence experiment, 1941?, (20 items) (Box 705)
      - Humphrey, B.: Stuart PDT and DT-X analyses, 1941?, (2 items) (Box 705)
      - Humphrey, B.: Rhine-Humphrey, terminal salience, 1941, (6 items) (Box 705)
      - Humphrey, B.: Interests and ESP, 1949, (3 items) (Box 705)
      - Humphrey, B.: Item analyses, undated (Box 705)
      - Humphrey, B.: Martin and Stribic analyses, undated (Box 705)
      - Kahn, S.: Mechanical scoring technique, 1949-1950 (Box 705, Opaperfolder 4)
      - Kapchan, J.: Dramatic group tests, undated (Box 705)
      - Killick, G.: Two-dice PK, 1949, (8 items) (Box 705)
      - MacFarland, J.: Machine-shuffle precognition, 1938-39, (3 items) (Box 705)
      - McMahan, E.: Self-testing club, 1949-52, (3 items) (Box 705)
      - Nielsen, W.: Student's sheep-goat experiment, 1955-56, (7 items) (Box 705)
      - Nielsen, W.: Mood analyses, undated(many items) (Box 705, Opaperfolder 5)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Rat Experiment, 1938, (2 items) (Box 705, Opaperfolder 6)
      - Pratt, J.G.: ESP Marbles, 1941 (Box 705)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Bindrim displacement papers, 1946, (9 items) (Box 705)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Gibson exploratory PK, 1946-48, (6 items) (Box 705)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Reeves PK position effects, 1947 (Box 705)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Target preference study, 1947, (2 items) (Box 705)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Restricted success in PK, 1947 (Box 705)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Change-of-call analyses, 1949 (Box 705, Opaperfolder 7)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Jessup ESP test, 1950(many items) (Box 705)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Forwald placement PK, 1950-51 (Box 705)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Direction finding experiments, 1951 (Box 705)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Homing records, 1951-52, (4 items) (Box 705, Opaperfolder 8)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Homing records, 1953-56Wayland pigeon project (Box 705)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Homing writings, 1953-58, (3 items) (Box 705)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Homing records, 1952-58 Germany, 1957 (Box 705)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Vasse first grade ESP, 1955-56 (Box 705)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Louwerens school experiment, 1959-1961, (6 items) (Box 705)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Perot ESP paper, 1961 (Box 705)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Miscellaneous data, undated, (2 items) (Box 705)
      - Pratt, J.G.: JBR-LER position effect analyses, undated, (4 items) (Box 705)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Miscellaneous, (2 items) (Box 705)
      - Rhine, J.B.: Rhine distance ESP, 1933 (Box 705, Opaperfolder 9)
      - Rhine, J.B.: Drug studies, 1935-39, (2 items) (Box 705)
      - Rhine, J.B.: Detroit PK study 1942(many items) (Box 705)
      - Rhine, J.B.: PK analyses, 1942-47 (Box 705)
      - Rhine, J.B.: Ratte game vs. standard PK, 1960 (Box 705)
      - Rhine, S.: SLR-BMH Wright Refuge experiments, 1948, (6 items) (Box 705)
      - Rhine, S.: SLR-BMC 1-2-3 experiment, 1952, (3 items) (Box 705)
      - Stuart, Miscellaneous, 1945-47, (5 items) (Box 705)
      - Van Busschbach: First American Series, 1956, (4 items) (Box 705)
      - Van Busschbach: Second American Series, 1960, (6 items) (Box 705)
      - Miscellaneous, (6 items) (Box 705)
      - Gibson, E.P.: Penny PK, 1944 (Opaperfolder 4)
      - Gibson, E.P.: Miscellany, (2 items) (Opaperfolder 4)
      - MacFarland, J. Machine-shuffle precognition, 1938-39 (Opaperfolder 4)
      - Smith, B.Th.: Drug series–ESP, 1938-39 (Opaperfolder 4)
      - Pratt, J.G.: Homing records, 1953-54 (Opaperfolder OC:IV:7, Opaperfolder 1)
      - Gibson, E.P.: Precognition (Opaperfolder OC:IV:7, Opaperfolder 2)
      - Correspondence experiment, 1938 (Opaperfolder 4)
      - Gibson, E.P.: Miscellany, (3 items) (Opaperfolder 4)
  - J. B. Rhine Miscellaneous Files Series
    - FRNM Files
      - G. Miscellaneous, 1964-66 (Box OV1, Opaperfolder 5)
  - Financial Papers Series
    - Payroll Control Sheets (Personnel), 1953-1957 (Box OV1, Opaperfolder 6)
    - Detail Budget Statement, 1954-56,Part I (Box OV1, Opaperfolder 7)
    - Detail Budget Statement, 1954-56,Part II (Box OV1, Opaperfolder 8)
    - Detail Financial Statement, March 1956-August 1958, McDougall Reserve Fund (Box OV1, Opaperfolder 9)
    - Detail Financial Statement, Sept. 1958-Oct. 1962, McDougall Reserve Fund (Box OV2, Opaperfolder 1)
    - Detail Financial Statement, ONR Contract, Fr. J.G. Pratt, March 1956-Feb. 1963 (Box OV2, Opaperfolder 2)
    - Detail Financial Statement, March 1956-Sept. 1962,Parapsychology Department (Box OV2, Opaperfolder 3)
    - Detail Financial Statement, Parapsychology (Box OV2, Opaperfolder 4)
      - Scholarship Fund, Oct. 1960-Dec. 1961 (Opaperfolder 4)
      - J.G. Pratt, March 1956-June 1962 (Opaperfolder 4)
    - Detail Financial Statement, March 1956-June 1962, J.B. Rhine (Box OV2, Opaperfolder 5)
    - Research/Experimenter/Pratt, J.G./Change-of-call analyses, 1949 (Box OV2, Opaperfolder 6)
  - Parapsychological Association Records Series, 2 containers (1 lin. ft.)
    Records relating to the tenures of Rhea White and J.G. Pratt as officers of the Parapsychological Association, Rhea White as the first secretary (1957) and Pratt as council member (1959-62) and President (1960). Included is correspondence among council members and papers relating to the association's annual conferences. Early documents relate to the development of the association's constitition and by-Laws.
    - 1961,Convention papers (Box OV1, Opaperfolder 5)
- Accession (2009-0089), (6 boxes)
  Accession (2009-0089) (8 lin. ft.; about 5670 items; 1930s-1970s) includes data sets, case files, correspondence, notes, reports, and lectures from Dr. J.B. Rhine and his wife, Louisa E. Rhine. Subjects include parapsychology research, ESP, animal homing, and psychics.
  This addition is unprocessed.
  - Correspondence to Dr. Rhine regarding experiences, 1965-1970 (Box 1)
  - Louisa Rhine materials, including letters and correspondence, A-Bs, 1961-1975 (Box 2)
  - Responses to Hidden Channels and The Mysterious World Beyond the Five Senses (Box 2)
  - ANPSI cases and materials, 1950s (Box 3)
    - Cats, dogs, birds homing cases (Box 3)
  - Reports, lectures, notes, and correspondence about pyschic experiences, 1940s-1970s (Box 4)
  - Experiment logs and record books, about 1935-1940 (Box 5)
    - EPG Distance experiments (Box 5)
    - ESP records (Box 5)
  - General correspondence, cases, articles, 1960s-1970s (Box 6)
- Accession (2009-0090), (9 boxes)
  The addition (2009-0090) (12.6 lin. ft.; 7000 items; dated 1930s-1980s) includes correspondence, case files, lecture notes, research data, and other materials from the work of Dr. J.B. Rhine and Louisa E. Rhine. Subjects include ESP, animals' sixth sense, psychics, and other parapsychology topics.
  This addition has not been processed.
  - General correspondence, printed materials, meeting minutes, notes (Box 7)
  - Correspondence regarding the Rhines' publications, 1960s (Box 7)
  - Reactions to J.B. Rhine's article, Do Animals Think?, 1950s (Box 8)
  - Animals PSI (Box 8)
  - Letters after L.E. Rhine's death, 1983-1985 (Box 8)
  - Files on J. Gaither Pratt and Gardner Murphy, 1979 (Box 8)
  - J.B. Rhine bibliography, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous obituaries and articles, 1950s (Box 8)
  - Foundation for Research on the Nature of Man, 1970s (Box 8)
  - The Essence of Parapsychology draft (Box 8)
  - ANPSI files, 1950s (Box 9)
    - Unconfirmed reports (Box 9)
    - Telepathy (Box 9)
    - Cases of awareness of approach (Box 9)
  - Notebooks from L.E. Rhine with data, 1960s (Box 9)
  - L.E. Rhine materials: letters, experiences (Box 10)
  - Correspondence among J.B. Rhine, L.E. Rhine, Dorothy H. Pope, and Dr. R. RAO, 1950s-1975 (Box 11)
  - Media correspondence (Box 11)
  - J.B. Rhine lecture notes (Box 11)
  - ANPSI cases, research, materials, 1940s-1960s (Box 12)
  - L.E. Rhine general correspondence (Box 13)
  - Case files, A-L (not filed alphabetically), 1970s (Box 13)
  - L.E. Rhine correspondence, 1960s (Box 14)
    - I. Freeman (Box 14)
    - B. Marck (Box 14)
    - Grice (Box 14)
    - M. Boyer (Box 14)
  - L.E. Rhine correspondence with teenagers regarding experiences and interest in parapsychology (Box 14)
  - Something Hidden draft (Box 14)
  - L.E. Rhine lectures (Box 14)
  - L.E. Rhine correspondence with editor at MacMillin and Grove (Box 14)
  - J.B. Rhine letters to Marie Higbee, around 1958-1964 (Box 14)
  - Research data and notebooks, undated (Box 14)
  - Journal index (binder) (Box 14)
  - Research and data files (Box 15)
  - Distance ESP tests, 1936 (Box 15)